[{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664066208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":22600,"timeElapsed":104616},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664087813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":21602,"timeElapsed":126220},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664100143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":12327,"timeElapsed":138551},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664115495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":15350,"timeElapsed":153903},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664123667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8169,"timeElapsed":162075},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":9898,"timeElapsed":171975},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5490,"timeElapsed":177467},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664141587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":179994},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664144013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2424,"timeElapsed":182421},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":18424,"timeElapsed":202267},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664169304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5443,"timeElapsed":207712},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9403,"timeElapsed":217117},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5327,"timeElapsed":222446},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9719,"timeElapsed":232168},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":11926,"timeElapsed":244096},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3726,"timeElapsed":247822},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664211615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":250023},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1971,"timeElapsed":251996},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":30165,"timeElapsed":283348},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5238,"timeElapsed":288588},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8197,"timeElapsed":296788},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5227,"timeElapsed":302017},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7745,"timeElapsed":309764},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2225,"timeElapsed":311991},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3789,"timeElapsed":315783},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":317984},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":320545},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664322425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":39201,"timeElapsed":360833},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4578,"timeElapsed":365413},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333738,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6731,"timeElapsed":372146},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7651,"timeElapsed":379799},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664344540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3146,"timeElapsed":382948},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7231,"timeElapsed":390181},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2461,"timeElapsed":392644},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2733,"timeElapsed":395379},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1625,"timeElapsed":397007},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":398924},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":16911,"timeElapsed":417031},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4241,"timeElapsed":421273},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":16149,"timeElapsed":437425},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664402718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3700,"timeElapsed":441126},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664405550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":443958},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2414,"timeElapsed":446374},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":448798},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":451817},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":453819},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":9785,"timeElapsed":464491},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664432598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6512,"timeElapsed":471006},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436559,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3958,"timeElapsed":474967},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6598,"timeElapsed":481567},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664447892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4731,"timeElapsed":486300},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664451464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3570,"timeElapsed":489872},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1661,"timeElapsed":491536},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3176,"timeElapsed":494714},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":498073},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":500490},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":15345,"timeElapsed":516782},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664481778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3402,"timeElapsed":520186},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664485823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":524231},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664489875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4050,"timeElapsed":528283},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":531397},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664494792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1801,"timeElapsed":533200},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664497140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2346,"timeElapsed":535548},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664500039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":538447},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664502031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1990,"timeElapsed":540439},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664519884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":16778,"timeElapsed":558292},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664523955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4069,"timeElapsed":562363},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4371,"timeElapsed":566736},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":569652},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664535709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4462,"timeElapsed":574117},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664539969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4257,"timeElapsed":578377},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664542653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2682,"timeElapsed":581061},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664544782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":583190},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664546521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1737,"timeElapsed":584929},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664557991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":10622,"timeElapsed":596399},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664562204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4209,"timeElapsed":600612},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4736,"timeElapsed":605351},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":608689},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664574524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4240,"timeElapsed":612932},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664576084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1558,"timeElapsed":614492},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":616823},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664580558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2141,"timeElapsed":618966},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664582380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1820,"timeElapsed":620788},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664592988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":9674,"timeElapsed":631396},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664595990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":634398},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":638392},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664603793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":642201},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664607337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":645745},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664609058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1720,"timeElapsed":647466},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664612000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2939,"timeElapsed":650408},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664613702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1699,"timeElapsed":652110},{"subjectID":"vvmbm7ysra","prolificID":"65ecc3670bbda5b4fb282ce1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742144ea9a49a640662c80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664615412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1709,"timeElapsed":653820}]